Hallelujah
If I may call a brother there -
the brother that decided to abandon wife and children and leave home.
They didn’t know, you just abandoned home.
You left everything for them and ran for your dear life
because a ‘prophet’ or a ‘pastor’ told you that your wife was whatever you call her.
I will not join you to call your wife that.
Come out. You abandoned your wife and you are here today.
You abandoned your wife and your children at home – you are looking for ‘freedom’.
‘Your wife is the one in charge of this, your wife is the one who wants to kill you,
your wife is the one that made you jobless’ -
no, come and hear God’s opinion.
God loves you.
Give thanks to God.
Give thanks to Him.
My name is Godwin Ebhohimen.
I am the man the man of God prophesied about that has left his family.
I live in Abuja, doing business.
A pastor said my wife is the one bringing me down
because my business and everything went down the drain.
Even now, I am indebted.
Because of that, I decided to run away from them.
Nobody even knows where I am now.
I am the one the man of God prophesied about.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Godwin Ebhohimen.
The woman standing right beside me is my lovely beautiful wife.
Last Sunday, I happened to be in The SCOAN where the man of God prophesied about a brother here
who had decided to abandon his home based on what he was told by a pastor
that his wife was responsible for his financial misfortunes.
He said I should come out and hear God’s opinion.
So, I came out.
Really, the prophecy is true.
In 2012, I was living in Abuja, doing my business.
I am into frozen foods, while my wife and children live in Edo State; she works there.
Every month, I visit them.
In 2012, customs seized my goods.
Early 2013, they seized more goods.
In 2013, we had our third baby.
We went to a church for the dedication.
During the dedication service, the pastor called my wife and both of our families
and told my wife that she was responsible for my downfall.
The families were crying and talking about it.
I told them to calm down.
He said my wife talked too much.
I told him that I knew the wife I married that she didn’t talk much or keep friends.
We went home.
The battle started.
In my home, there was no peace.
Any little thing that happened, I would recall the prophecy.
I quit my business because of financial problems and started another business.
That one – a car business also went down.
I went into property; that business also went down.
Any time I had financial difficulties, I would refer back to the message of that pastor
that my wife was responsible for my financial downfall.
It got to a point that even my children were sent out of school, the house rent was not paid
- so many problems.
Whenever I thought about that message, I would just take my bag and leave home.
It would be months before I returned home.
Mr Godwin Ebhohimen & Wife
Prophecy Testimony
I had a property in Abuja that I decided to sell so that I could travel and leave this country.
I put it up for sale but nobody would buy it.
After going to three different agents, the property remained on the market.
Early this year, when we had a quarrel again and the children were sent out of school
and the landlord was disturbing us, I decided to leave for good,
to look for a way to sell the property and leave the country and live my life.
I left my wife and three kids.
I was in Ogun State and came to Ajah.
On Sunday, I came from Ajah to The SCOAN.
I decided that as I was leaving the country, I would change my sim card.
- No coming back to your wife...
- No coming...
When you finally came to the church - what happened?
When I came to the church, my aim was to get the Morning Water,
to sprinkle it on that property and see if God would give me the grace to sell the property and get out.
When I came here, I had the opportunity to get the Morning Water.
As soon as I got the Morning Water, I danced and felt happy that I would sell the property.
As I was dancing, I heard the man of God mention my case.
I was a bit reluctant but something pushed me and I came out.
The man of God gave the prophecy and I was asked to wait.
As I was waiting in the evening around six thirty something,
I received a phone call while I was in the church from one of the agents
stating that she had a buyer who wanted to negotiate for the same property
that nobody had called me about since last year.
When that call came, I said, “Wow, this is God who is in control. God is really here!”
We just want to ask you a question.
You said the message came forth and it pointed to your wife as the architect of your downfall.
Based on the fact that you were experiencing downfall,
you had to relate your misfortune in life to your wife.
That developed hatred and you abandoned her and the children.
Ever since you have abandoned her and the children, before you came to The SCOAN,
was your life really good?
Life was not good because so many people who I was owing were calling me, here and there.
At a point, I stopped wearing my wedding ring.
She would call me and ask where my wedding ring was.
I would tell her that ‘ring’ was not the problem, that it was the heart that was the problem,
so she shouldn’t care about the wedding ring.
Life was really miserable.
After the prophecy you received from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua telling you that
you are wrongly accusing your wife - what happened afterwards?
After that prophecy, I was waiting to see the man of God as he had directed when a call came in.
It was that call that really confirmed it to me - "Yes, this is God speaking."
When the call came in, I was happy that God had located me.
I called my wife to tell her where I was.
That same Sunday, she called me around 4pm when I was in church;
I told her not to worry, that I was safe and OK.
After the prophecy, on Monday morning, I called her and told her that I was in The SCOAN.
Before the prophecy, any time she called you, you didn't want to give her any attention,
because you still saw her as the architect of your problems?
Yes.
But after the prophecy, you intentionally gave her a call?
Why did you have to call her after the prophecy?
Because I believe and confirm the prophecy is true.
Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
Having heard from the man of God that you were wrongly accusing your wife and you were misinformed,
what is the state of your mind concerning your wife now?
Right now, she is the best woman on earth.
Immediately I called her, I went to search for where I had kept my ring and put it on
before seeing her face to face.
Once again, shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
What word do you have for your wife right now?
I have to beg her to please forgive me.
It was wrong information that was driving my heart.
Please, forgive me, my honey, my love.
That is not enough for Jesus Christ - put your hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Right now, we want to hear from our madam.
We believe she is shedding tears of joy, because old things have passed away, all things have become new.
Right now, ma, to the glory of God and to the shame of the devil,
tell us your name, who is the man next to you and what you have to say about what your husband has said.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning everyone.
My name is Mrs Ebhohimen.
The man beside me is my husband.
We are from Edo State.
We got married in 2007 – November to be precise.
Within that time, our marriage was very sweet and loving.
It was not until 2012, when his business went down the drain.
In 2013, we had our third baby.
When we went for baby dedication in our local church, I invited friends; our relatives were there.
When it was time for the baby’s dedication, I carried my baby, right on the altar.
Everybody had followed me there to celebrate with me.
All of a sudden, the man of God told the whole church that he had an announcement to make - a prophecy.
He said, “This woman you are seeing here is the architect of her husband’s financial downfall”.
I stood there, speechless
waiting for my baby to be dedicated.
After the announcement he made, the dedication continued.
When we went home, things went the other way.
I saw another man in my husband.
I could no longer see my husband.
He no longer enjoyed my meals.
At the smallest quarrel,
he would ask me how was I sure that I was not the architect of his financial downfall.
Since then, life had not been easy for me.
At times, he would just leave the house.
On my return home from work, I would not meet him there.
He would not even speak a word or give a dime for the family upkeep.
Then, I had borrowed money from many people because he had left me and my children behind
and I was left alone to take care of my kids.
My salary was no longer enough for me to pay the debts I owed.
I continued borrowing to the extent that my salary was exhausted.
I would go out and buy food on credit to feed my children.
We strongly believe old things passed away, all things have become new.
Though it wasn't easy, but all to the glory of God.
This is the day the Lord has made and you will rejoice in it.
We strongly believe that you are only reflecting on a past issue,
knowing fully well that God has taken glory - restoration and reconciliation have come.
The vision is very clear now and to God be the glory.
My prayer then was for God to vindicate me and take away the garment of shame from my life.
On Monday last week, I had a phone call.
I was told the call was from The SCOAN, that my case was mentioned
and they wanted to see me here, on Saturday.
I left Edo State on Friday and came here yesterday.
I met my husband; they told me the prophecy.
I was so happy that at last I had been vindicated.
That is not enough for Jesus Christ - put your hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God.
To God be the glory.
It is a clear proof that when all hope is lost, Jesus Christ revives our hope.
No one is hopeless whose hope is in Christ Jesus.
Having received and honoured the call and meeting your husband, ever since then,
what are the changes you have noticed to confirm that the Lord has come to stay in this family?
The first change I noticed was his wedding ring because for a very long time, he had not put it on.
When I saw him yesterday, he was wearing the wedding ring
and I knew that God had restored my marriage.
To God be the glory.
Having gone through all this, right now you are vindicated.
As a woman, we believe you are in the best position to advise women out there.
If not for your patience, assuming you would have also taken a nasty step,
today there wouldn't have been anything like reconciliation.
You bore the situation, you were able to be patient, to persevere until today,
that the Lord has brought reconciliation to the family.
What word of advice do you have for women out there, how to handle issues like this?
It wasn’t easy for me as a woman.
It was the grace of God that kept me in the marriage ‘til today.
A day came when he told me he was tired of me and that I should leave.
I told him that I was not leaving the home because God said the two become one,
that we did our wedding in the church and I would never leave him.
I told him wherever he went, he must come back.
This has been the faith that has been keeping me.
My advice to my fellow women out there that have been blacklisted and called ‘witch’,
I want to advise you that there is nothing the Lord cannot do.
The Most High who has used our Prophet T.B. Joshua to vindicate me,
will visit you, in the name of Jesus.
To God be the glory. Our belief is that they have keyed into this advice.
We believe this advice will go a long way to bring a reconciliation to many families,
and give hope to women out there, who are facing similar situations,
as the Lord has taken control in your life.
Let's hear briefly from your husband.
With all said and done, we believe you are convinced that the Lord is good.
What word of advice you have for men out there?
My advice to the whole world is that whatsoever the situation, difficulty
or name they call our partner, loved one or people around you, don’t be in a haste to act.
Search for the mind of God towards that thing that is happening.
God would surely provide an answer, in Jesus’ name.
To God be the glory.
You heard it all; when you are in a haste to achieve something, you are likely to make a costly mistake,
that will pull you back if not down.
Having harkened to this word of advice, we also want to encourage you as a couple
having known that the Lord is good, and your coming together is for good, for better or worse,
if you go and maintain your relationship in Christ Jesus,
always have it at the back of your mind that better is not good enough, the best is yet to come.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ.
Shortly afterwards, Mr & Mrs Godwin came back to The SCOAN
to testify to the goodness of God in their marriage.
Let’s listen to them.
My name is Godwin Ebhohimen.
I am the man the prophet prophesied about who abandoned his wife and children.
I give God the glory for locating me in that wonderful service.
Since that prophecy came, God has really changed my life.
I thank God that my family, my wife and I have been reconciled.
The love of God has started growing in our lives and I believe God that this reconciliation
that God used the man of God to bring to our lives is going to be permanent ‘til death do us apart.
I thank God today that God in His infinite mercy looked upon me and my family.
There have been great changes since this prophecy came to me.
I thank God for this prophecy.
I can see happiness, God’s love and unity.
We discuss things we didn’t discuss before.
Those are some of the changes I have started to experience.
Glory be to Jesus Christ.
We thank God for what He has done in your life.
Tell us what is the way forward from here.
The way forward from here is for me to commit myself to God the more.
I pray God will give me the grace to serve Him in humility, righteousness and faithfulness.
Thank you very much.
We want to hear a word from your wife as well.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs Ebhohimen.
The man beside me is my lovely husband.
I came to The SCOAN through a call from the man of God, here,
that my case was mentioned here in a Sunday service.
Since the reconciliation, I have seen love like never before.
There is peace and joy now.
Anything my husband thinks in his heart, he will tell me, which he didn’t use to do before.
I give God the glory.
Glory be to Jesus Christ.
We thank God for this beautiful reconciliation,
that God Almighty has used Prophet T.B. Joshua to perform in this marriage.
As you are here, and you are going back to your destination,
Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners have sent us to you with a cash gift of 100,000 Naira,
for your upkeep, future plans and endeavours, in order to support you,
to be able to succeed in whatever you want to achieve in life.
With it you also have one Mirror book for your spiritual growth.
I am shocked and overwhelmed.
I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners for this wonderful gift.
It is God’s grace for me to receive this.
I thank the Emmanuel TV partners and Prophet T.B. Joshua.
May God increase them.
May God increase his family, his ministry and his anointing, in Jesus' name.
Amen, glory be to Jesus Christ for what He has done in your life.
We know that this cash gift will go a way, in order to strengthen this family
and to make sure that you will be able to establish your family and your house in a right way,
for the glory of God.
We also want to encourage you to make God's Word the standard for your life,
so that everything you received here shall be permanent in your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank You, Jesus!
TT robert begier 28/02/2019
RV: Mel Flowers 16/03/2019